SEYED MOHAMMAD

SHEIKH AHMADI

CONTACT INFO

E-mail smsag99@gmail.com , info@sheikh-ahmadi.ir

Phone +39 3518371745

Address Turin, Italy

Website sheikh-ahmadi.ir

ABOUT ME

I am a Data Science student at **Politecnico di Torino** and also extremely passionate about programming and research. I founded a firm named VGostar in the Augmented Reality (AR) field at the University of Kurdistan, and also we have been funded by university.

Recently, I have been working in an accelerator firm named **Zharfa** as a back-end developer using Node.js. We are working on some commercial projects.

In 2021, I participated in a research project managed by Dr. Sina Ahmadi from the George Mason University and Dr. Fatemeh Daneshfar from the University of Kurdistan. It is supposed to be submitted soon.

EXPERIENCE

CO-FOUNDER AND BACK-END DEVELOPER

2022-2023

VGostar | Sanandaj, Iran

• Implementation of AR technology

JUNIOR BACK-END DEVELOPER

2022-Present

Zharfa Accelerator Academy | Sanandaj, Iran

• MicroLearning Project

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER ENGINEERING

2018-2022

University of Kurdistan | Sanandaj, Iran

- Accepting and being funded a firm related to AR technology by the university
- Research assistant (RA) and teaching assistant (TA)
- Student Union

MASTER OF DATA SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

2023-PRESENT

Politecnico di Torino | Turin, Italy

VOLUNTEER

RA

- Research assistant in **EndoLink** Project with **Dr. Sina Ahmadi** at George Mason University and **Dr. Fatemeh Daneshfar** at University of kurdistan.
- Research assistant in **KurdNet** Project with **Dr. Sina Ahmadi** at George Mason University and **Dr. Fatemeh Daneshfar** at University of kurdistan.

TA

• Teaching assistant of "Fundamentals of Computer Programming" course with C programming language, with **Dr. Amanj Khorramian** at University of kurdistan.

STUDENT UNION

Member of IOT student union

PROJECTS

MICROLEARNING

• Back-end of a commercial project at Zharfa Accelerator. source

MEMORAL

• Desktop Project for selling product in shops and stores. source

SKILLS

Hard SkillsNode.js , Linux, JacaScript

• Prisma, PostgreSQL, Mongoose, Redis

Docker-Compose

Familiar with • Java, C, C#, ASP.net, Python

Unity, Arduino, Jekyll

Languages • Englis

English IELTS 6.5 (Full professional proficiency)

Persian (Native)

Kurdish (Native)

REFERENCES

Dr. Sina Ahmadi Postdoctoral Researcher George Mason University sahmad46@gmu.edu

Dr. Amanj Khorramian Assistant Professor University of Kurdistan a.khorramian@uok.ac.ir

Dr. Fatemeh Daneshfar Dean of Department of Computer Engineering

University of Kurdistan f.daneshfar@uok.ac.ir